# **Schabse Laks**

Web Developer at Google

# Summary

I'm an experienced developer in the New York Area.

I've been programming in VB6 since 2002; in C# since 2005, and for the web since 2007.

I primarily use C# with ASP.Net MVC (for web) and DevExpress (for WinForms), and Javascript, jQuery, CSS, and LESS for web client development. I also know Java (although I don't like it) and C++ (although I've never written any code in it), and I'm familiar with Python, Ruby, C, and C++.

In my quest to help people better understand these languages, I've risen to the top ten users on StackOverflow.

I haven't found the time to learn any functional programming languages; I make up for that by writing functional-style code in C# using LINQ and lambda expressions.

# Experience

## **Developer**

March 2014 - Present

Frontend development for Google Classroom

#### **CTO**

February 2005 - Present

Database work, website, printed materials, billing system, and all development

## **Developer at Unroll.me**

June 2012 - March 2014 (1 year 9 months)

Wrote a fully asynchronous Java IMAP client capable of maintaining 10,000 connections on small AWS machines

Rewrote the main unroll.me website in Node.js using DerbyJS

## **Consultant at Caretech Group**

April 2012 - June 2012 (2 months)

Worked on an existing ASP.Net MVC LOB application.

### **CTO**

September 2011 - May 2012 (8 months)

I created the website and backend systems for a startup.

However, the startup's idea did not work out and I am now moving on.

# **Consultant at Morgan Stanley**

May 2006 - August 2011 (5 years 3 months)

I've worked at Morgan Stanley for a number of disjoint summer internships during high school and college doing various kinds C# data work

# Education

**Yeshiva University** 

Dropout, Math, Computer Science, 2010 - 2012

Activities and Societies: Honors program

# **Schabse Laks**

Web Developer at Google



Contact Schabse on LinkedIn